We see this target as likely very
achievable. Boom. Wow. That's freaking
awesome. That's almost as awesome as
Lauren offering us a special flash sale
and meet Kevin.com. Today only. In this
video, we're going to provide an update
on SpaceX, including the email that I
just got, which is in my opinion big
news for people with a SpaceX exposure
or maybe who want SpaceX exposure. Keep
in mind, I personally have exposure to
SpaceX in my venture capital fund. The
better SpaceX stock does, the better I
do. So, I want to be clear about that.
We haven't sold a single share. People
have been asking me, "Oh, but Kevin, you
know what? What price would you add at?"
We've already made videos on that. We'll
talk about that in a little bit. But in
this video, I'm going to break down a
bullish email that I got. Then, we're
also going to look at what Goldman Sachs
is saying and what Deutsche Bank is
saying. And forgive me for just being a
little clear when I point out like,
"Yes, we're long. No, we're not short."
Because some people seem like they just
leave a comment and then leave and they
don't actually watch. And I I think the
vast majority of us, 99% of us,
appreciate very clear and consistent
information. And that's my goal here. Uh
and and so that does make me positively
exposed, but I also want to be realistic
about the stock. And that's where my
this is where I would add to the stock
price targets come from. Okay, first
let's start with the bullish email. So
the bullish email is actually right
here. It is an update for our venture
capital exposure in SpaceX. We've got uh
probably multiple seven figures in in
SpaceX. Actually, certainly multiple
seven figures in SpaceX. uh which is
exciting since we invested back at, you
know, 300 uh billion-ish dollars and uh
we're uh we're well above that at this
point. So, we're excited about that.
We'll see where it ends up when we
actually get the shares, how much we
actually have, what the dilution was and
all that. I don't know. But you'll find
that this email was sent this morning on
August 10th. If you remember, today is
Lauren's birthday. So, Lauren is giving
a little bit of special juice on a flash
sale. We're going to have a coupon
expire on Friday, but today only we're
doing a little bonus flash sale. So, if
you join with today's coupon code,
you'll get a little extra. And that is a
shout out to Lauren uh for for
suggesting that. So, go check that out
over at meetke.com. You can get that
lifetime access to the alpha membership.
But take a look at this. Here's the
latest information that I have. Once the
SpaceX funds fund continues with the
unlocking process, you will see SpaceX
fund shares slowly uh start showing
common stock. A little bit of the right
side of this email got cut off. I I'll
show you a little bit more detail of
that in just a moment. Once the common
stock is in your account, we can hold
the shares, sell a portion of shares, or
sell all of them. This is a financial
adviser. Now, this is the line that I
think is the most interesting, and I'm
going to actually pull up a better
screenshot of it. It's right here. They
say, "I have found that the that most
clients plan to hold the shares." That's
actually kind of cool. You know, that's
kind of a way of saying people are
looking at this like a long-term call
option. And that's why we also got to
look at the long-term debt exposure that
this company's likely to get itself
into. Uh so uh you know here's where
they talk about the distribution process
and how it's going to take in my opinion
basically weeks to actually get the
shares unlocked because there's so much
bull crap that needs to go on in the
background. Who cares? That's all suit
crap. Doesn't matter to me. What matters
to me uh are these three different
institutional pieces and then we're
going to look at uh something very
important here in the earnings for
SpaceX. So, uh, first, Goldman Sachs
and, uh, Deutsche Bank are relatively
bullish on the stock. There are a couple
changes here that, you know, somebody
sent me these documents and I'm like,
"Oh, okay. I I hadn't thought about it
this way, but I always like kind of
seeing what the suits are saying." Some
of the suits are now suggesting we could
get up to five launch pads by the end of
2027, the end of next year. It's not
that far away for the Starship. Now,
obviously there's a lot of execution
risk baked into this, but that's higher
than the four that I thought. And I
thought four was going to be a lot. You
know, we're like at one functional right
now, right? So, getting to the five by
the end of 27, that's pretty good
because it kind of helps you get more
launches going, especially since that V3
uh that'll, you know, 10x the bandwidth
capabilities for Starlink apparently
doesn't fit in the Falcon 9 rocket. And
that might be part of the reason why
they're not taking orders for the Falcon
9 rocket anymore anyway past 2029
because they just want to send bigger uh
you know lower cost per kilogram uh
ships into space basically. There uh was
talk uh here from Goldman about how
Arpoo for Starlink exceeded their
expectations. I honestly think these
companies sandbagged their expectations
because if I look at Deutsche Bank, I
could see that Arpoo was $66. Actually,
this one's labeled Goldman, but it was
definitely Deutsche Bank. Um, let's
verify that. Yeah. Yeah, this is the DB
logo right here. So, this one's DB. But
anyway, uh, Arpoo was flat a quarteron
quarter at 66 bucks. That's down quite a
bit from $85 last year. Uh, 66 is the
new number works out to a decline of
about 23.5%.
I guess that's not as bad as we thought
when we initially saw SpaceX was doing
like 50% off coupon codes for people to
join uh Starlink. And I think there's a
this idea that once you hook people in
and they get their dish and it's
installed, they're probably likely to
keep paying. It makes sense. It's a good
product. It's a good service. So,
doesn't surprise me that they lower
their prices before IPO and then raise
their prices right after IPO. It's sort
of like, hey, let's show how much user
growth we have and we'll slow it down
after IPO. I think that's a little bit
what's happening here. Uh, satellites in
orbit exited the quarter at 10,200
versus the 9.6 expected. I think a lot
of these institutional writeups are
honestly sandbagged on purpose so they
can say, "Wow, everything beat
whatever." What I think is most
interesting is that SpaceX is targeting
5 to 10 gawatt in 2027 of compute. Now,
we've seen Elon talk about this and we
talked about what I call the bifurca
bifurcation or the cataclysm in
artificial intelligence investments. Uh,
this morning we made a video on it and
we talked about how on the left side on
one side you've really got frontier
level compute. You know, that's like
Anthropic signing a deal with SpaceX.
Anthropic also just signed a deal with
Riot, the former, you know, crypto
mining company. They signed a $9 billion
cloud deal with them. I mean, they're
like, you know, they'll sleep with
anybody to get compute at this point.
And and Elon knows that. And so Elon's
like, I want to have the biggest boobs.
I want to attract the most anthropic I
can because they'll pay me a premium.
We'll talk about that in just a moment.
But this bifurcation here that we're
having is really between a frontier,
which is, you know, the latest and
greatest LLM, your latest and greatest
coding, whatever. Uh and then of course
you're going to have your openw weight
models not to be confused with open AAI
which is obviously not openw weight. Uh
so open weight and this is going to be
your enterprise. Um in my video this
morning we really talked about how this
is likely to take over a lot in the
future and you know we made some
commentary around what we think would be
great investments for this side winning
but SpaceX doesn't have anything to do
with this side in my opinion. you know,
they're they're not going to provide
5090s for us. They're not going to
provide RTX 6000 black wells. They're
not going to provide little workstations
for businesses who actually put AI to
work, like reinvest
SpaceX. And you have to know this if
you're investing in SpaceX. I don't, you
know, I just want to be clear about it.
SpaceX wants the highest freaking margin
compute possible. They don't give a crap
if you're going to use Alibaba's Quen.
They don't give a crap if you're going
to use Meta's, you know, openweight LLM.
What SpaceX wants is to make as much
money from the highest margin homies
possible. You know, we heard about this
$500 billion joint, you know, Black
Rockck and Jensen deal with Nvidia uh
this morning. You, you know, like $300
billion of that is probably going
straight into Nvidia's pocket. They love
this, man. It's a giant circle. And
Nvidia prints money uh and Nvidia is
going to print more money over here and
so is SpaceX. You know, SpaceX prints
money selling to these frontier people.
So, as long as the Frontier people keep
spending like crazy, Elon's going to
keep spending like crazy and providing
it for them, great. These are different
investment strategies, right? If you
want that exposure to the frontiers, you
get that Nvidia, you get that SpaceX. If
you want exposure to enterprise AI the
way it's actually changing businesses
or or you know building ROI for people
like I think what we're doing with
reinvest you know those are not the two
plays there are different options there
and they're actually not in hardware at
all. You could actually even make the
argument that over here you know you're
going to have the Marll. I mean we just
made a video on this. The Marll, the
LSCC,
uh the Microns, right? Those all fall
under this side. That's really important
to reiterate here because I just want
SpaceX investors to know that when
you're investing in SpaceX, you are
investing for that frontier LLM. None of
that open weight stuff matters to you
because you're not going to get the
margin from there in my opinion. Now, is
it possible that SpaceX will in the
future host Enterprise AM AI sort of
like an Azure or you know um I don't
know any of the other providers maybe,
but that's not where the high pay is
right now. So, you want the big margin
dollars to be over here where Anthropos
spend god-awful sums to make sure they
get to AGI, which I, you know, I think
is a scam. I don't think it's going to
happen, but that's fine. You know,
whatever. SpaceX, it doesn't matter to
SpaceX. It's like, sign the contract and
pay us. We don't care if you get AGI or
not. But anyway, um the estimates of 5
to 10 gawatts by 2027. This is actually
really important because you know if I
go look at the balance sheet for SpaceX,
you're going to find something here.
We've got $93 billion of cash plus uh
6.4 of marketable. We've got about
hundred billion of cash, right? We have
about $13 billion in bills. You'll find
that right here under current
liabilities. And I take the deferreds
out. So, you know, that gives us about
$86.9 billion to work with. That's
great. But capex for SpaceX is probably
going to go from $18 billion a quarter
to $25 billion a quarter to my guess is
going to be somewhere around $50 billion
per quarter. So, I honestly think that
86 billion, this is my prediction, $86.9
billion maybe makes it to year end, but
Elon is going to blow it. Like, I
shouldn't say blow it. That sounds bad.
Spend it all. Okay, he's going to spend
it all. $86 billion is going to get you
like 2 gawatt. Okay, 86 billion equals
about 2 gawatts of compute. You want
those Vera Rubins. You want the best
Vera CPUs and the the GB300s. You want
the best uh or or the Reubins. You want
the best possible product. It's going to
cost you closer to $50 billion a
gigawatt. And so that next 8 gawatt is
going to cost you probably somewhere
around $400 billion. And so if I add
that together, I I need probably to be
safe $500 billion. I need an extra $414
billion. So where is $414 billion going
to come from? Well, that $414 billion is
not going to come from the cash flow
statement because the cash flow
statement is already getting burned by
capital expenditures going into rockets
and and satellites, right? Like I'm I'm
excluding the uh the the AI investments
here which represent about 85% of this.
Uh if so, if I take this and multiply
that by about 85, that's about 24.2.
That leaves me with about yeah about
$4.2 2 billion dollar going to rockets
and the other parts of the businesses.
That means we are negative cash flow,
right? We basically spend all of our
operating cash on the space and
communications business, the
connectivity business, Starlink, right?
That's fine. Then on top of that, we're
investing an extra in in this case in
the last 6 months $24 billion into
compute. That in my opinion on a
six-month basis is going to get to the
point, mark my words, where it ends up
saying hundred billion. That would work
out to $50 billion on actually it might
even be more than that. That that might
on a six month. Yeah. 6 months. 100.
Yeah, cuz this is six months. Six
months. Yeah, that's that's right. 100
billion on the six months. That would
work out to 50 billion on the quarter
and that would work out to about 200
billion on the year. That's I think what
it's going to say. So you you know
you're really going to get aggressive
here in the spending. And then the
question is
where's that money going to come from?
Yeah. 50 billion per quarter, 100
billion on 6 months, 200 on a year. That
seems appropriate. And if we get to 200
on the year, that means by the end of
2028, Elon's probably spent all of the
money. Uh all $500 billion. You know,
maybe it takes until the middle of 2029,
but before the end of the decade, he's
going to blow half a trillion dollars.
He is a trillionaire after all.
Uh anyway, so I think he's going to make
this investment that's going to be
really good for those downstream
frontier beneficiaries that we're
talking about in this bifurcation side,
right?
He hasn't announced raising that extra
money yet, though. And the question is
where is that going to come from? Is it
going to come from share sales or is it
going to come from more debt? Well,
management argues it's going to come
from debt. Now, financing as just XAI
sucked because they were paying 12.5%.
That sucked. But they've actually
derisked SpaceX and now, you know,
basically the compute side is the more
expensive side to finance, but they've
derisked it drisked it with Starlink and
Starships, which is great. And so
they're actually able to borrow on
30-year fixed well 30-year notes at
6.65%.
And 5-year notes at 5.35. Now, at the
time, that was about 115 basis points
more than the equivalent yield of the
5-year or 30-year Treasury at the time.
If they went to borrow again today, it
would probably be even more expensive
just because rates have gone on up even
more. I mean, the 10ear is at 4.7,
partly because of this Iran drama that
just unfortunately keeps going. Yeah.
The the 30-year right now is at 5.25.
The 5-year Treasury, if we pull up the
current uh on it, it is sitting at 4.41.
H 4.41
4.41 plus 1.15. they'd probably be
borrowing at about 5.56. So, an extra 20
bips or whatever here on the 5-year. Not
horrible, but the point is this also
isn't cheap debt. It's not like China
who's borrowing at, you know, 1.9%.
China has lower inflation, so they say,
so their yields are substantially lower
than ours in America. Uh, but even
though this looks like expensive debt,
it's way cheaper than if XAI were
standalone. And it's way cheaper than
what Coreweave is borrowing at, which is
borrowing at over 10% as well. So SpaceX
actually made this debt cheaper to get.
And so I think they'll keep issuing debt
here. I do think at some point it will
become I I should make that note here
will become cheaper to issue stock. And
because there are A and B classes, Elon
doesn't have to dilute his ownership of
the company by issuing stock to common
shareholders to us retail people.
This means that if SpaceX continues its
retracement here, there will come a
point where they'll just decide to issue
stock instead of taking on more debt.
But I think the vast majority of what
they take on will be more debt. Deutsche
Bank thinks they'll get to about $300
billion of debt by the end of the
decade. That would mean they'd probably
have to issue 300, you know, well,
they'd probably issue somewhere around
$275 billion of debt. and and and then
in my you know with my math maybe a
couple hundred billion dollar
140ish billion dollar worth of equity.
So I think you're going to get a
combination between here and there and
that's a lot. That's a big raise.
Remember Google was in the process of
raising and still is about $80 billion.
And you know it hasn't been horrible. it
like the market's been doing okay, but
Google peaked out when they said they
were going to issue $80 billion and so
it's been tough for them to get past
this 374 level. You can see this reject
reject reject reject over and over and
over again. If you look at actually the
uh SpaceX technicals, we can see we
really tried to break out of 13334
today. We struggled during most of the
day. Look at this clean rejection. Clean
rejection. Rejection. Rejection.
Rejection. Right at the end of the day,
that to me looks like leveraged ETF
buying. Right at the end of the day,
right at the end of the day, you get
this pop. That's almost certainly ETF
buying, especially the leveraged ETFs.
Almost certainly.
But, um, but that's an important line
for SpaceX because it's your next
retracement line and we've been holding
that pretty well. So, uh, my my belief
and and I maintain this, uh, you know,
and and we I try to pat myself on the
back, but we were right when we said
there was a shot this was going to run
up 30% and there was going to bleed out.
It's literally exactly what happened.
And now I try to pat myself on the back.
It's just, okay, so what do we think is
going to happen next now? Well, we could
keep seeing this retracing mostly
because it takes so long for these
shares to lock up. And the benefit of
this or free up, I should say. The
benefit of that is people are going to
look and go, "Well, it's rising. Why do
I need to sell?" So, the very lockup
pressure that might cut and run if the
stock's in freef fall might see the
stock slowly climbing up and then I'm in
no rush to liquidate. Why why sell? You
know, you're still going to see some
selling pressure. And I'm not sure that
it's actually hit yet uh in terms of of
those locked up shares. Obviously, we
had selling pressure over here, but uh
uh you know, this this is good. Hey, you
you want to see if you want the entire
economy to hold up, you want to see
SpaceX do well because they're going to
keep spending money on artificial
intelligence, uh, you know, frontier
level chips and it just keeps the
circular economy going, which ultimately
trickles down to everybody else. Oh,
less plebs.
Now, anything else in these
institutional notes to look at? Well,
again, my opinion, they're going to
issue a lot of debt and they're going to
have to issue shares by the end of the
decade. uh unless they just want to go
into the end of the decade with like,
you know, $400 billion dollars of debt,
which maybe they will. I don't think
they're going to pay off any of their
debt anytime soon. I did think this was
very bullish here by Deutsche Bank.
Deutsche Bank here suggests that Cursor
has annual recurring revenue of $4
billion in June. And in their
projections to get to a hundred billion
dollars of annual recurring revenue by
the end of the year, their projections
are that SpaceX is going to be able to
3x Cursor's
uh annual recurring revenue. I think
that's very very hopeful.
Maybe they could pull it off. Uh but I
think the biggest component is actually
the Neocloud side here. And on the
Neocloud side, Goldman actually argues
that they're likely to hit it. Take a
look at this. So, if I go right here,
uh we got the five launch pads. Where is
the $100 billion? Well above the right
over here. This is where they talk about
uh the uh pricing per gigawatt hour.
Even Goldman's like, "Wow, they're
signing contracts for well above our
long-term assumed pricing per gigawatt."
There's a lot of debate about this. the
the people who are blind bulls get mad
at me when I'm like, "Wow, these prices
are kind of ridiculous per gigawatt hour
that um you know, SpaceX is charging." I
think there might be something else
going on here. Like maybe Google is
willing to sign these ridiculous prices
because they hold $95 billion of SpaceX
stock. 95% of their entire equity
portfolio at Google is SpaceX.
But anyway, uh you know, people get mad
at me for saying that, so whatever.
Obviously, there's some debates here. Uh
SpaceX has obviously uh established a
dominant position within the market.
That's fine. Here, this is where they
also talk about having 10 gawatt of
terrestrial compute within the next 2
years. That two years, you got to come
up with the money for that. Within the
next two years is before the end of
2028. They're going to have to come up
with 400 billion bucks. I love the word
terrestrial as well, not to be confused
with extraterrestrial. So you're
basically like, hey, you know, you
borrow money and build it on Earth. Keep
in mind, like 40% of that is expected to
go to the big guy. The big guy in this
case is Jensen,
not to be confused with any other big
guys. Star like Arpoo. Okay, where the
heck was that note? I'm going to find
it. But anyway, there is a little note
where they break down how much is going
to come potentially on a per uh hour GP.
I found it per uh hour GPU basis and how
they're going to add up this annual
recurring revenue. So, first of all,
they actually say we see this target as
likely very achievable. Boom. Wow.
That's freaking awesome. That's almost
as awesome as Lauren offering us a
special flash sale and meet Kevin.com
today only. All right, take a look at
this. We see this target is very
achievable to triple SpaceX's ARR annual
recurring revenue by December.
Wow, that's really bullish. But then in
fairness, when we add it up, I could see
how they get there. I've got 3.75 from
Anthropic. I've got another 3.3 from the
government according to Goldman here. Is
this Goldman? Nope. Deutsche Bank again.
Sorry. Uh, plus Google at three billion
a quarter. Well, that alone right there
puts you at uh three or 10.1 billion a
quarter. Okay, that's already $40
billion ARR right there. And then if you
add in a mystery one, that gets you
halfway to the 100 ARR by December only
for the Neoclouds, not including
Starlink
launch services
uh you know X whatever.
Now this is obviously the odd table here
and this is the pricing per uh GPU hour.
We could see that uh Deutsche Bank's
estimates are that Anthropic is only
paying somewhere around $5 per GPU hour,
which is appropriate. About 755 for the
GB200's, about 350 for the H100's.
Totally appropriate. Uh for the latest
and greatest chipsets here though, the
GB300,
you've got a whole range over here. You
got 11.45, 1175, and $6.96
at a larger purchase right here. So, it
seems like when somebody comes in and
wants to have a bulk order, they get
like 50%. Okay, maybe not 50% off, but
6.96 divided by, you know, divided by
1155. That's 40% off, man. That's a
pretty good coupon code. That's like a
flash sale right there. Not to be
confused with a memory. Uh but anyway,
they do say there is some risk that
Google could end up terminating because
they're just at such an expensive level.
I honestly don't think so because they
own way too much SpaceX stock to
terminate.
Uh and then of course Vera Ruven is
expected to deliver up to 10x token
efficiency relative to Blackwell. Uh and
those were some of the other estimates.
So you know let's let's put all this
together. Let's take out the whiteboard
here. People always like it when I bring
up the whiteboard. I think I don't I
don't know. I say that, but you have to
leave me Oh, you have to leave me a
comment if that is true. But what I'm
going to do here is I'm going to write
down when I buy and when I sell.
Um,
if we get uh Okay, so this is going to
be the sell and and I'll send an alert
when and if I sell to everyone who's a
course member, but this will be a
trigger. Okay. If RSI
on the weekly
is over this number,
that's going to be a sell. Okay. And
then for the buy, for a long-term
buy, I want to be able to acquire this
uh between the two prices that I'm
listing here. Above that, I'll I'll like
in between that range, I'll hold. Okay.
above that range uh I'll you know above
the RSI I'll sell and uh and and if we
get to this target that's what we'll buy
ready for it right here RSI weekly
exceeds 69 okay relative strength index
that's not a price you could see the uh
RSI right now on the weekly basis is 55
so we're accelerating here okay I don't
think we're going to get to 69 anytime
soon. I would probably say honestly it
probably has to be 69 and 200, right?
Like if it goes up to 149 tomorrow, I I
mean the RSI weekly won't be there at
69, but it probably something like this.
Okay, so RSI relative strength index
weekly over 69 and $200 a share. At the
very least, you set some trailing stops.
Uh, and then the buy for for long-term
investing probably somewhere around
here. That's where I feel there's
actually some margin of safety because I
honestly I think they're going to take
on a crapload of debt. Like Elon doesn't
care. This is this is his mission. This
is his hurrah, baby. Hurrah.
So anyway, my take. I hopefully I've
been transparent enough here and if I
piss some people off on social media
want to make some content and make fun
of me. Well, that's all right.
I still love y'all and I'm still going
to provide my point of view. Thanks for
watching. We'll see you in the next one.
Goodbye. Good luck.
>> Why not advertise these things that you
told us here? I feel like nobody else
knows about this.
>> We'll we'll try a little advertising and
see how it goes.
>> Congratulations, man. You have done so
much. People love you. People look up to
you.
>> Kevin Pafra there, financial analyst and
YouTuber. Meet Kevin. Always great to
get your take.